Ok I have my cornmeal, my beaten egg, add just a 1/4 cup of sugar just to sweeten it up.
It's not going to be sweet like a corn muffin or anything but, cornmeal is pretty not sweet, it's going to be a little sugar in there.
1/4 cup of sugar, 1/4 cup of vegetable oil, just kind of combine and bring that together.
We are going to add some milk, we are going to mearsure out a cup and I'm going to add it slowly.
Just ot kind of see how much we need, I'm going to start with about a 1/2 cup.
Let's just start with a 1/2 cup.
Mix this together and see, yeah, we may not even need much more than that. Yeah, that's coming together nicely. Beautifully, kind of see how that's coming together, starting to look like cornbread!!
Well, cornbread batter, get a good look at that.
Still a little thick, so I'm going to add just a little bit more of the milk.
So that's just over a 1/2 cup, what I added.
You know depending on how big of a batch you want to make of this, double it.
You know use 4 cups of the cornmeal and you know, just double everything else from there.
Alright, that's looking pretty good, about where I want it.
See the consistency nice.
This is not a huge batch of cornbread, really isn't.
So it's going to just be really thin in this pan, but that's OK and again it's going to cook up quickly and it's not going to matter because we are going to break it up and put it in our larger dish anyway, so it's doesn't even matter.
We get this pan, so we can get in the oven.